<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProjectRelief</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome back!</string>
    <string name="hey_you_leveled_up_good_job">Hey!You leveled up, good job!</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="yoga_asanas">Yoga asanas</string>
    <string name="healing_music">Healing music</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="rise_and_grind">SWASTHA</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="yoga_fragment">Yoga Fragment</string>
    <string name="yoga_name">YOGA NAME</string>
    <string name="new_fragment">New fragment</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="sub_title_of_asana">sub title of asana</string>
    <string name="categories">CATEGORIES</string>
    <string name="music">#MUSIC</string>
    <string name="relax_says">Relax, says</string>
    <string name="para">Yoga-like practices are first mentioned in the Rigveda as a non-Brahminical practice.[9] Yoga is referred to in a number of the Upanishads.[10][11][12] The first known appearance of the word "yoga" with the same meaning as the modern term is in the Katha Upanishad,[13][14] which was probably composed between the fifth and third centuries BCE.[15][16] Yoga continued to develop as a systematic study and practice during the fifth and sixth centuries BCE in ancient India\'s ascetic and Śramaṇa movements.[17] The most comprehensive text on Yoga, the Yoga Sutras of Patanjali, date to the early centuries of the Common Era;[18][19][note 1] Yoga philosophy became known as one of the six orthodox philosophical schools (Darśanas) of Hinduism in the second half of the first millennium CE.[20][web 1] Hatha yoga texts began to emerge between the ninth and 11th centuries, originating in tantra.[21][22]Yoga (/ˈjoʊɡə/ (listen);[1] Sanskrit: योग, lit. \'yoke\' or \'union\' pronounced [joːɡɐ]) is a group of physical, mental, and spiritual practices or disciplines which originated in ancient India and aim to control (yoke) and still the mind, recognizing a detached witness-consciousness untouched by the mind (Chitta) and mundane suffering (Duḥkha). There is a wide variety of schools of yoga, practices, and goals[2] in Hinduism, Buddhism, and Jainism,[3][4][5] and traditional and modern yoga is practiced worldwide.[6] Two general theories exist on the origins of yoga. The linear model holds that yoga originated in the Vedic period, as reflected in the Vedic textual corpus, and influenced Buddhism; according to author Edward Fitzpatrick Crangle, this model is mainly supported by Hindu scholars. According to the synthesis model, yoga is a synthesis of non-Vedic and Vedic elements; this model is favoured in Western scholarship.[7][8]</string>
    <string name="yoga_asana_name">YOGA ASANA NAME</string>
</resources>